your name, your address, and even
your phone number.
Somebody can be pulling it all up in
a single search.
An independent Deloitte Assurance Report confirmed
Incogni covers at least 420
data broker websites and private databases.
But when you look specifically at broker coverage,
third-party reviews put Aura's list at over
200 sites.
So if your goal is getting your name off as many
sites as possible and as many types of
sites as possible, Incogni currently
covers more ground.
Now, that sounds good on paper, but don't you already
have a VPN?
If you do, you're basically paying twice for tools you
don't need.
You can use the code CODEWORD for 60% off
Incogni's annual plan.
Your data is already out there whether you
like it or not.
So the question is, what are you going to do
about it?